l don't know what my next move is.
(Leonard:)Well, Howard, I don't know
much about women.
- Yeah?
- No, that's it.
l don't know much about women.
(Leonard:)Raj, you got anything?
l've got the phone number
of the tubby girl from Comic-Con.
(Howard:)I'm not calling the girl from Comic-Con.
(Raj:)All right, more Sailor Moon for me.
l just threw up the bachelor party.
(Penny:)Please come out, Bernadette.
Let's talk through this.
(Bernadette:)No, leave me alone.
(Amy:)You should give him a taste of his own
medicine. Have a cousin you find attractive?
(Amy(into a mini-cam):)Amy.
Hey, you introduced her to the sleazebag.
I'm just trying to clean up your mess.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi.
l need to talk to Bernadette.
(Penny:)Well, I don't think she wants to
talk to anyone right now.